http://www.soundmatters.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - SOUNDMATTERS
0
No products in the cart.
Pro Spotlight Series
Soundmatters LIVE!
Pro Spotlight Series
Soundmatters LIVE!
16193
page-template-default,page,page-id-16193,theme-bridge,woocommerce-no-js,,qode-title-hidden,side_area_uncovered_from_content,columns-4,qode-theme-ver-10.1.1,wpb-js-composer js-comp-ver-6.2.0,vc_responsive
Privacy Policy
Privacy & Security
Because your privacy is important to us, Soundmatters has prepared this privacy web page so that you may better understand how your personal information is used in connection with Soundmatters’ online services. Please take the time to review this page and contact us at info@soundmatters.com with any questions or concerns.
This Statement of Privacy & Security applies to the Soundmatters website, customer telephone surveys, product registration cards and customer support helpdesk communications and governs data collection and usage at soundmatters.com and all Soundmatters services. Soundmatters provides a general-audience website. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy & Security.
Collection of your Personal Information
Soundmatters may ask you to register and provide personal information in certain instances, such as when you purchase products from the Specialty Store, register new products, enter a contest or sweepstakes or sign into a page that requires authorization. Soundmatters may also collect financial information to bill you for products and services that you purchase online.
This personal information may include your name, email address, user ID, address and telephone number. Soundmatters may also collect demographic information, such as your age, gender, zip code/postal code, education level, household income, preferences, interests, favorites and whether you are a personal or business user.
Collection of Other Information
System Configuration Information:
Soundmatters may automatically collect on our server logs certain information about your computer hardware and software when you visit our website. This information may include: your IP address, cookie information, globally unique identifier system, operating system, description of any Soundmatters products connected and how such products are used, browser type, domain names, access times, service provider and referring website addresses. This information is used by Soundmatters to monitor the operation of our website and online services and the use of its products, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of our products and our website.
Tracking of Website Usage:
Soundmatters also tracks the usage of visitors to our website, including the URL of the visitor’s previous website and when they exit our website. Soundmatters also keeps track of the pages our customers visit within our website and any transaction details (downloads, orders, requests or referrals) in order to determine what Soundmatters products, information and services are the most popular. This data may also be used by Soundmatters to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Soundmatters may use various technologies to track trends in the use of our website or online services, including session cookies and GUIDs. These allow us to track how consumers interact with Soundmatters online and, only with your permission, this information may be tied to your personal information to help us tailor communication to you.
Use of Your Information
With your express permission, Soundmatters may collect, integrate and use this personal and other information to help you quickly find software, services or information on soundmatters.com, to help us create website content and other services most relevant to you and to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, newsletters, updated information and other new services from Soundmatters. When Soundmatters receives information about your session or about you, we may use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you. We may also use this information from time to time to monitor the technical functions of our servers and site. Soundmatters uses this information to communicate with you only after you give your express permission for such communication. Soundmatters does not share this information with any third parties, except with your consent or as described below.
If you choose not to register and provide this information, you can still use most of Soundmatters’ services. Unfortunately, you will not be able to access areas that may require registration.
If you do not want soundmatters.com to send you email or postal mail regarding Soundmatters products or services, you may opt out when you register by selecting the option stating that you do not wish to receive such marketing materials from soundmatters.com by selecting the option stating “Check here if you do not wish to receive Soundmatters mailings”.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
From time to time, we supplement the information we collect from the site with information from offline or third party sources. We use this information to enhance or overlay the profile of customers and business contact information. This supplementary data is therefore tied to corporate contact information and in some cases personally identifiable information.
We also may internally compare lists collected from our other sites or within our family of companies to remove duplicate entries.
Soundmatters will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your approval, except that we reserve the right to disclose your personal information: (a) to any of our affiliates, subsidiaries, third-party service providers or advisers that we deem appropriate; (b) if such disclosure is made pursuant to a legal proceeding or as required by law; (c) if necessary, to protect the personal safety of users of Soundmatters’ website, or the public; (d) to protect and defend the rights or property of Soundmatters, including its website; (e) to another business entity should we plan to merge with, or be acquired by, that business entity; or (f) organizations involved in a merger, transfer or sale of our assets or business.
In the event that we disclose your personal information as set out above, we will require third-party organizations who have access to your personal information to protect and maintain your personal information in compliance with the terms and conditions of this Statement of Privacy & Security.
Control of Your Personal Information
Soundmatters offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information at the time the customer decides to register. In addition, you may also stop the delivery of future communication from Soundmatters by unsubscribing at any time. For instance, each email you receive contains instructions explaining how to stop receiving such emails.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code/postal code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can be done by emailing support@soundmatters.com.
Security of Your Personal Information
Soundmatters is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Collection and Use of Children’s Personal Information
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. If for some reason we are made aware we have such personal information we will take reasonable steps to delete that information.
Use Of Cookies
Like many other companies, Soundmatters uses cookies to help you personalize your online experience. We use both session and persistent cookies. A cookie is a very small text file placed on your hard drive (with your permission) by a web page server. It is essentially your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies are used to tailor content to your interests. For example, when you initiate a response by clicking on a link within an email message, you are re-directed onto the Internet. We then record your individual response to help us deliver information that is more relevant to your interests. This saves you time as it helps Soundmatters remember who you are. It makes your subsequent visits to soundmatters.com simpler and more seamless. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. However, on some pages which require authorization, cookies are not optional. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will likely not be able to access these pages.
Use Of Globally Unique Identifiers
What is a GUID?
A Globally Unique Identifier (GUID) is an alphanumeric identifier used to indicate a unique installation of a product, and is found in many popular software applications such as web browsers and media players. Soundmatters may use GUIDs for aggregate statistical analysis, to personalize products and services.
Soundmatters’ Use of GUIDS in LDM products and in future products
LDM randomly generates a GUID during installation. Soundmatters uses publicly documented standards to generate GUIDs. From time to time, Soundmatters may use a GUID with a unique set of numbers in order to gather and aggregate information about traffic patterns, such as how many times a user attempts to access content from a server. These statistics help us improve our services.
We may collect data marked by Soundmatters GUIDs in order to understand aggregated traffic patterns and other Soundmatters usage patterns. We use this data in order to measure product performance, better understand types of content that are popular with our users and how our products are used and to conduct user surveys. We may relate GUID marked system data to other personal information supplied by users. The system information that is linked to your personal information is limited to information about the types of Soundmatters products you have connected to your computer. Further, consistent with our privacy principles, Soundmatters does not sell or share such information with any third party unless we obtain a user’s advance informed consent.
Use Of Email Messaging
Soundmatters may periodically send our registered users email messages about our products and services. When sending you email, we may use an image called a single pixel GIF that allows us to format messages tailored to your computer’s capabilities. We also use this technology to determine, in the aggregate, how many people open our emails. When you initiate a response by clicking on a link within an email, you are redirected onto the Internet. We then record your individual response to help us deliver information that is more relevant to your interests.
Changes To This Statement
Soundmatters will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy & Security. When Soundmatters posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word “updated” next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of soundmatters.com. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Soundmatters will use your personal information, Soundmatters will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change; however, we will not make any changes that are less protective of your personal information collected in the past, without your consent. Soundmatters encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Soundmatters is protecting your information.
Company
Our Story
Management Team
Dr. Guenther
Markets Served
News & Press
Contact Info
775.981.1460 ext 2
[fts facebook page id=soundmattersinc posts_displayed=page_only type=page]
@soundmattersinc
[fts twitter twitter_name=soundmattersinc]
[fts instagram instagram_id=218357424]
Soundmatters News
Michael Fremer, Analog Planet: Soundmatters UPstage 360 Not a Coffee Maker But Brews Up Immersive Sound
Henry Rollins: “I never go anywhere without the Dash7”
© 2018 Soundmatters International Inc. | 800.698.SOMA (7662) • 775.981.1460 Terms of Use
| Privacy Policy
| Product Photos
English
